

Filip Rastovic

PROFILE

Name	Filip Rastovic
Year of Birth	1993
Languages	English / Serbian

CONTACT

Email	filiporastovic@gmail.com
Skype	filiporastovic

I grew up in Sremska Kamenica, suburban neighborhood of Novi Sad, where I also finished elementary school. As a kid I would spend my time reading comics, epic fantasy novels and playing video games. During high school I played guitar in the school orchestra and worked on technical support and special effects for the school theatre. During college I started developing small video games as a hobby and began my career as a freelancer utilizing everything I've learned through education and on my own. I'm passionate about technology and developing creative solutions to whichever problem I come across. I'm an avid reader and music lover.

Professional **Resume**

EXPERIENCE

2015 - present

Web Developer/Designer

HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript/Web Design/UXD

Experience in coming up with original web designs, coding responsive semantically correct markup of the design and then adding dynamic features using jQuery/other libs. Experience in A/B (recording the behavior of users and changing the design accordingly).

2015 - 2016

Private Programming Lessons

OOP/Java

I lectured high school students teaching them basics of object oriented programming and Java.

EDUCATION

2012-2016

Faculty of Technical Sciences

Computing and Control Engineering

Department of applied computer science and informatics. I have understanding of data structures, computer architecture, object oriented programming, design patterns, software engineering methodologies and web development concepts. I'm also familiar with HCI concepts, machine learning and web security.

2008-2012

"Svetozar Marković" Gymnasium

Novi Sad

General course.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML5 JavaScript Photoshop Responsive Web Design Usability Testing
CSS3 jQuery Wordpress User Interface Design Conversion Rate Optimization

Bootstrap3/4 php React.js User Experience Design Adobe XD

SCSS git Angular.JS Landing Pages

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS



GAME DEVELOPMENT



CLASSIC LITERATURE



GUITAR



COMPUTERS



OUTDOORS



TRAVELS

Filip Rastovic filiporastovic@gmail.com